The Coffin Family Papers
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
Coffin Family Papers
September 11, 1810 – January 2, 1859
NPKMC-222-071
0.3 Linear Feet
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
Hudson River Sloop Clearwater, Inc.
The Coffin Family Papers contains bills, promissory notes, receipts, account ledgers, bonds, deeds and other documents relating to the business and personal transactions of Robert Coffin of Dutchess County, NY.
Collection Overview
The Coffin Family Papers contains bills, promissory notes, receipts, account ledgers, bonds, deeds and other documents relating to the business and personal transactions of Robert Coffin of Dutchess County, NY. Certain documents reflect the judgments made by Coffin as Justice of the Peace. The collection also contains many important documents relating to the death of Colonel Tabor Bently, father-in-law to his executor Robert Coffin.
The Coffin Family Papers was donated to the Marist College Archives and Special Collections by Enid Mastrianni of Glens Falls, NY, who purchased the documents privately.
Biographical Note
The Coffin family can trace their line back to Sir Richard Coffin of Devonshire. He was born circa 1280. The first Coffin to come to America was Tristram Coffin, born January 4th, 1628. He was a direct male descendant and was fourteen generations removed from Richard Coffin. Tristram traveled from Devonshire, England to what was then New York (now part of Massachusetts) in 1642. Tristram was among a group of 9 men who bought the island of Nantucket from the Native Americans in 1659 for 30 pounds and 2 beaver hats.
Abishai Coffin, a fourth generation descendent from Tristram, moved from the family seat in Nantucket and settled in the Hudson Valley as the American Revolution loomed. One of Abishai's sons was Robert Coffin who represented Dutchess County in the New York State Assembly in 1832 and who is the focus of this collection. Robert was born in 1778. He served his county in the capacity of Justice of the Peace and was reportedly a very able and amiable man. He married Magdalene Bently, daughter of Colonel Tabor Bently and left ten children when he died in 1842 at the age of 64.
The Coffin family is currently spread across the whole of the United States. They figure in politics as well as many other notable facets of American life. Prominent Coffins include Levi Coffin, who was known as the “president” of the Underground Railroad, Lucretia Coffin Mott, a moral reform activist, suffragette and teacher of Daniel Anthony, father of Susan B. Anthony and Professor James Henry Coffin, who made contributions in the fields of astronomy, meteorology and geometry. Dramatist “Tennessee” Williams was the grandson of Isabel Coffin, writer O. Henry has ties to the family and prolific character actor and namesake of the Coffin progenitor, Tristram “Tris” Coffin appeared in countless roles in early television shows from Superman and The Lone Ranger to I Love Lucy and The Beverly Hillbillies. The Coffins, noted Quakers, were avid abolitionists and equal rights activists. The numerous descendents of Tristram Coffin were very successful. In the year 1828 alone, 26 of them graduated from New England universities, 15 of those from Harvard. Though many Coffins still live in Nantucket, a large branch of the family is settled in North Carolina and, thanks to Levi Coffin, another branch exists in Indiana. Many of the Coffin line also reside on the West Coast.
There are no restrictions on the collection
Collection is arranged into one series with materials being roughly chronological. Each folder is seperated loosly by subject or document type.
- 1. Coffin Family Documents, 1
  - Folder 1: Robert Coffin’s Labor Receipts, 1811-1859; 1; Boxes: 1 Folders: 1-11
    The documents in this collection consist of bills, promissory notes, receipts, account ledgers, bonds, deeds and other documents relating to the business and personal transactions of Robert Coffin of Dutchess County, NY.
    Roughly chronological
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by William Rozull - February 6th, 1824, 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Murinus Pierce for lumber - September 25th, 1830, 2 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by W.D. Sherman for Freights Issued by John Titus - September 20th, 1811, 3 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Garrison McCoy - January 26th, 1820, 4 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Samuel Thorn - January 4th, 1819, 5 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Matthew Collins - February 17th, 1819, 6 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Ledger of financial transactions between Robert Coffin and Henry D. Davis for shoe and boot repair. - January 2nd, 1839 - December 10th, 1839, 7 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Stock account of Robert Coffin - 1843, 8 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Promise of funds (payment complete) from Robert Coffin to Gabriel L. Vanderburgh - April 28th, 1829, 9 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by George Wright - October 11th, 1822, 10 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Isaac Bayce - February 28th, 1831, 11 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Smith Narrick for plaster - May 2nd, 1821, 12 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Sahuzher Germond - October 23rd, 1823, 13 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Joseph Wright - May 28th, 1833, 14 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Murinus Pierce for lumber - June 22nd, 1833, 15 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Ledger and Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Henry D. Davis for shoe and boot repair - September 16th - November 20th, 1830, 16 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Ledger and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Isaac Woolley for lumber - July 7th - August 28th, 1829, 17 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by C.P. Barnum - December 19th, 1829, 18 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Running bill (May 18th - Nov 24th) and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by F. Warner for fresh meat - January 2nd, 1859, 19 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Henry D. Davis for shoe and boot repair - 1831, 20 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by C. Morgan for furniture, 21 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Stephen Allen - May 1, 1813, 22 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Samuel Thorn for services rendered - January 13th, 1820, 23 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Jacob Benthicysins - October 7th, 1823, 24 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Theodore Van Wyck and Cornelius Van Wyck - November 8th, 1833, 25 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Lymon Hustid for shoe and boot making - January 20th, 1835, 26 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by William Tillou and Henry Tillou - December 9th, 1822, 27 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Gabriel L. Vanderburgh, executor for George Toffey (deceased) - April 1829, 28 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Promise of payment (fulfilled) by Robert Coffin to John Hoag, administrator of the estate of Peter Hoag (deceased) - May 7th, 1829, 29 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Promise of payment (fulfilled) by Robert Coffin to Leonard L. Seaman - June 8th, 1821, 30 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by William Haywood for labor services rendered - April 3rd, 1824, 31 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Samuel Seaman - December 13th 1822, 32 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Bill and receipt of payment from Robert Coffin by William Odell for clothing - December 1831, 33 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Ira Odell Jr. - July 20th, 1824, 34 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by James Odell for Elizabeth Titus - January 11th, 1819, 35 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by C. Morgan - June 21st, 1823, 36 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Abraham Gager - March 20th, 1825, 37 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Document authorizing Robert Coffin to sell the worldly possessions of Henry Odell to extract payment due to him of $27.00 - March 31st, 1842, 38 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Ashael Hall - April 19th, 1829, 39 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Running bill for Obediah Griffin, Jacob Odell, John Odell, Alonzo Griffin, Charlotte Doughty, Henry Gril, T. Farrenside and Mary Davis (each separate), 40 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds by Isaac Germand - July 15th 1818, 41 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Stephen Hammond - August 16th, 1820, 42 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Ledger of credits and debits between Robert Coffin and P. Schermihorn, 43 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Henry Odell - January 29th -February 25th, 1833, 44 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Alexander Marshall and Martin Haight - July 27th, 1821, 45 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Doctor F. Vanderburgh - May 26th, 1821, 46 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Joseph Gildesleu - January 16th, 1830, 47 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from John Titus, John Haight and Robert Coffin as a result of the partition and sale of real estate left by Archer Macomber (deceased) by Refcom Macomber - July 11th, 1833, 48 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Promise of payment (fulfilled) by Robert Coffin to Silas Gammond - May 1st, 1826, 49 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Promise of payment (fulfilled) by Robert Coffin to Sarah Upton - July 5th, 1821, 50 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Culois Rider - January 26th, 1833, 51 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Promise of payment (fulfilled) by Robert Coffin to Israel Shadbolt - September 8th, 1832, 52 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Promise of payment (fulfilled) by Robert Coffin to Ruben Howes, John Haight, Henry Marriott on or before May 1, 1824 (paid April 3rd, 1823), 53 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by J. B. Benton - November 18th, 1828, 54 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by J.B. Benton - August 1, 1827, 55 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Bill to Robert Coffin from Hezekiah Fhienstea - January 26th, 1824, 56 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by William Rogers - July 6th, 1815, 57 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Joshua Gager - May 28th, 1818, 58 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Promise of payment (fulfilled) by Robert Coffin to J.T. Derthick - May 5th, 1828, 59 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Joil Benton - December 3rd, 1827, 60 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by William Girmond - June 2nd, 1828, 61 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Promise of payment (fulfilled) by Robert Coffin to Isaac Girmond - January 12th, 1824, 62 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin to Emanuel Carinau - May 10th, 1828, 63 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin to Jefse D. Sarls - November 2nd, 1832, 64 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Thos Hammond - January 30th, 1823, 65 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Boriah Swift for damages - July 21st, 1826, 66 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds from Tabor Bently by Robert Coffin for damages awarded through the supreme court of New York - January 10th, 1824, 67 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Receipt of funds (in advance) from Robert Coffin by B. B. Benedict for advertising - September 11th, 1810, 68 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Folder 2: Tappan Families; John Brown, Folder 2; 1
    - Promise of payment by Robert Coffin to Margaret Amurman for value received - April 3rd, 1839, 69 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bill from John Charles Brown to Robert Coffin, 70 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by George Tappan - April 18th, 1830, 71 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Folder 3: Legal Judgments made by Justice of the Peace Robert Coffin, Folder 3; 1
    - Receipt of funds from Henry D. Davis by Job Sifson as ordered by Justice of the Peace, Robert Coffin - May 5th, 1830, 72 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Ledger of Credits and Debits involving Joshua Dulong and Robert Coffin. Balanced paid in full - June 13th, 1828, 73 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Letter of judgment in the case of Simon B Benton, Isaac Thorn and Israel Gibson VS P.B. Thayer. Robert Coffin, Justice of the Peace, ruled in favor of Benton, Thorn and Gibson (two pages), 74 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Receipt of funds by Joseph Doty from Daniel T. Butts as ordered by Justice of the Peace, Robert Coffin - May 14th, 1822, 75 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Original Cemetery Deed to lot 6 West Point: plot 6 in the village of Glen’s Falls made out to Emma Doty and sealed to by the president of Glen’s Falls, Samuel D. Kendrick and witnessed by Edwin R. Stafford, Notary Public, 76 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Folder 4: Newspaper Receipts, Folder 4; 1
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by P. Potter for Poughkeepsie Journal papers from no. 1444 to 1511, 77 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Ambrose Peck for Poughkeepsie Telegraph papers from no. 1 to 50 - April 14th, 1825, 78 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Killey Low for Poughkeepsie Telegraph papers no. 312 to 364 - April 17th, 1833, 79 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Ambrose Peck for newspapers - January 1st. 1830, 80 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Killey Low for Poughkeepsie Telegraph papers no. 197 to 312 - May 28th, 1831, 81 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Ambrose Peck for Poughkeepsie newspapers - January 8th, 1827, 82 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Ambrose Peck for Poughkeepsie newspapers - January 1st, 1827, 83 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Eliphalet Wood for newspapers - January 29th, 1819, 84 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by E. Lyons for Observer newspapers up to no. 176 - September 20th, 1818, 85 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Folder 5: Bills and Receipts from the Vail Family, Folder 5; 1
    - Promise of payment (fulfilled) by Robert Coffin to Hiram Vail - February 9th, 1821, 86 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Bill from Israel Vail to Robert Coffin for services performed in court, 87 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Hiram Vail for five days work - March 18th, 1827, 88 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Folder 6: Bills for the Schooling of Robert Coffin’s Children, Folder 6; 1
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Nathan Burton Jr. for Charles Coffin for the school winter 1826-7 - March 24th, 1827, 89 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by J.P. Brall for Miss Coffin for tuition, school expenses, textbooks and entrance - April 21st, 1818, 90 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Stephen Welletts for 44 days of schooling, fire wood and repairs and textbooks - May 1st, 1824, 91 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Enoch Haight for school bills - May 3rd, 1822, 92 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Leonard Goodwin for Miss Sarah Coffin for board from May 31st to August 23rd and school expenses, 93 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Sarah Pierce for J. Coffin for school expenses - August 22nd, 1824, 94 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Nathan Burton Jr. for Hezekiah and Sarah Coffin for the school winter 1825-6 - March 14th, 1826, 95 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Folder 7: Weaving Receipts, Carding and Dying, Folder 7; 1
    - Running bill and receipt of payment from Miss Sarah Coffin by Goodwin and Galpin for sewing and writing supplies - June 24th - August 19th, 1826, 96 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by S. Wood for sewing - March 25th, 1833, 97 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by P. Lawton for carding sundries - May 21st, 1832, 98 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Jeremiah Wintringham for weaving - April 2nd, 1827, 99 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by George Booth for carding sundries - August 28th, 1830, 100 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by C.P. Barnum for wood carding - November 14th, 1828, 101 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Jeremiah Wintringham for cloth - June 3rd, 1828, 102 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by A. Merritt - December 26th, 1826, 103 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Jeremiah Wintringham for weaving - April 10th, 1831, 104 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by John Wintringham for weaving - May 1st, 1824, 105 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Miss Sarah Coffin by Charles L. Webb - June 27th, 1821, 106 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Miss Sarah Coffin by Leonard Goodwin - August 23rd, 1826, 107 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Henry Gildersleeve - April 1st, 1826, 108 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Andrew Kingsley for dying - January 23rd, 1823, 109 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by John Wintringham for weaving - May 2nd, 1822, 110 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Henry Barton for carding - October 2nd, 1821, 111 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by John Wintringham for weaving - March 16th, 1818, 112 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by John Wintringham for weaving - March 20th, 1825, 113 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Jeremiah Wintringham for weaving - May 12th, 1834, 114 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Jeremiah Wintringham for weaving - March 16th, 1835, 115 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Matthew Collins for weaving - February 4th, 1819, 116 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by P. Howland and R.Y. Vary for painting and repair of a sleigh and wagon - January 28th, 1825, 117 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Folder 8: Official Deeds: Wills, Guardianship and Indenture, Folder 8; 1
    - Official deed of the Dutchess County Office Surrogate declaring the Infant Maria Stisker, aged sixteen in the guardianship of Robert Coffin until her twenty first birthday when she may collect the Estates granted to her by her father, James 1825, 118 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Last will and testament of Phebe Sarles witnessed by Robert Coffin and Peter Palmer of the town of Washington in the County of Dutchess, New York State - May 4th, 1842, 119 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Official bond binding Tabor Bently, his heirs, executors or administrators to Robert Coffin and Wheeler Gilbert for $1334.94 and list of items and money given to Coffin and Gilbert in fulfillment of the bond. Issued January 1st, 1821, fulfilled April 12th, 1827, 120 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Indenture binding Tabor Bently, his heirs, executors or administrators to Henry Able for $35.00 and receipt of items and money in fulfillment of the bond. Issued May 21st, 1825, fulfilled April 11th, 1826, 121 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Folder 9: Tabor Bently Inventory and Estate, Folder 9; 1
    - Inventory of the property belonging to Tabor Bently upon his death, as appraised by Daniel Stuart and Lewis Baker. s in the inventory willed to Tabor Bently’s daughter Eliza Bently. All approved by the executors of the will of Tabor Bently: Robert Coffin and Abnor Olsen - April 3rd, 1826, 122 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Ledger of credits owed by the estate of Tabor Bently (deceased) to Robert Coffin - April 11th, 1826, 123 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin, executor, by James Hooker for the return of the inventory of the Estate of Tabor Bently, 124 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin, executor, by Eliza Bently for money paid for grave-digging, 125 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Receipt of finds from Robert Coffin, executor, by James Hooker for the probate and recording of the will of Tabor Bently - April 5th, 1826, 126 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Statement of time of death of Tabor Bently - 1600h March 19th, 1826 and inquiry by Robert Coffin, executor, of the entitlement of a minor grandchild to the estate - April 1st, 1826, 127 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Handwritten tag or band titled “Tabor Bently’s Papers 1821”, 128 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin, executor, by Persis Sweet for demands against the estate of Tabor Bently (deceased) - March 17th, 1827, 129 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin, executor, by Solomon Dennis - March 16th, 1827, 130 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin, executor, by Albro Simpson for demands against the estate of Tabor Bently (deceased) - March 16th, 1827, 131 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin, executor, by Daniel Emigh for wares and merchandise sold to Tabor Bently during his lifetime - March 17th, 1827, 132 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin, executor, by Lewis Baker for bearing a chain around the farm of Tabor Bently - December 16th, 1826, 133 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin, executor, by S. Small - April 13th, 1827, 134 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin, executor, by Daniel Sweet for services as an appraiser - April 3rd, 1826, 135 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Settlement of the bill for Tabor Bently’s judgment bond, given to Robert Coffin, executor - January 1st, 1821, 136 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Text of the bond, settled in a separate document, of Tabor Bently to Wheeler Gilbert and Robert Coffin, executor - January 1st, 1821, 137 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin, executor, by Nicholas Emigh for demands against the estate of Tabor Bently (deceased) - March 14th, 1827, 138 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin, executor, by Allen Butler for running Tabor Bently’s (deceased) farm - October 11th, 1827, 139 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin, executor, by E. M. Stirft for suits in the name of the estate of Tabor Bently (deceased), 140 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Estimate of the affairs of the estate of Tabor Bently (deceased) made by Robert Coffin, executor - September 22nd, 1839, 141 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Robert Coffin, executor, by Lewis Baker for demands against the estate of Tabor Bently (deceased) - March 16th, 1827, 142 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin, executor, by Lewis Baker for demands against the estate of Tabor Bently (deceased) - April 3rd, 1826, 143 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin, executor, by Dennis Meriani for goods, wares and merchandise in the name of the estate of Tabor Bently (deceased) - March 17th, 1827, 144 (Box 1, Folder 9)